Where did we stop?
343 or
yes?  Where is he?  343. He is trying to find
where 343 is in his
text.  I don't mind
starting there.  Then who is she talking to?  For 10
dollars.  who is she talking to.
Misunderstanding, wrong worldview.
She speaks of a wrong
worldview.
By the way, I heard that you
finished your images pictures,
right?  And I heard that I will
receive them from every house tomorrow.  Yes.  And I heard
that you did a great job, but I need to
wait until tomorrow, right?
She calls him ignorant.  Do you
think you are a master or someone
else?  No, we talked about that
.  You don't have the strength and you
don't have And you don't even have what creates
your good
qualities.  We will now begin with
verse 332.  You say that nothing
depends on nothing.
that things do not
change, that nothing
depends on anything.  For you, everything is immutable,
motionless and strong and
never changes.  In your opinion, nothing at all
can
exist.
And then it exists, that nothing
can exist.  Not directly.  Someone
said the answer in the hall.  Not directly.
Of course, you understand that things
change.  I don't know, you're hungry after
lunch.  You sit in these long
classes and you get hungrier
and hungrier, thinking about your
food.  No one can say that things do not
change.  Ignorance does not mean that
things do not change.  He never
said that.  Why does she
accuse him of saying this?  That is, here it is
said about angels who unite
the devil.  I taught Geshil courses.
If one person gives all the answers, he
says: "Have you already told him all the answers
to the questions or have you already helped him
answer them?"  Yes, I told
him.  This means that Geshela is waiting for
someone in the room to answer.
So,
listen.  If things don't come from
your seeds, they would never
change.  In your mind, you think things
happen from there, from the outside
in.  100 dollars.  Who would say this in
Tibetan?
I didn't choose him.  The Thief must have raised
his head.  In this country, you can
win the most for the elections, but
that doesn't mean you'll be the
president of this country.  He jokes about
Trump's election.  Someone said
that a person who thinks that everything
happens by itself does not know this
question, so to speak, in
Tibetan.  OK.  And I wrote in the chat too
.  And Angeli
answered, which means that something is coming
towards us.  it's
coming towards us.  It's how you see things.  And what
is an
aria?  Aria means one who has touched the
diamond world
directly.  It's the
opposite.  Doesn't mean aria.  They
think the world is happening to you.  They
don't understand that the world comes from you.
And it leads me to bring us to the next
question.  How am I doing with
cash today?  I can't.  I don't
trust you.  Ready?  This is very easy
money.
If your family asked you why you
took a week to go to the diamond
mountain, you would answer.  I made more
money than if I had stayed at home.
So, the question is.  Are you ready?  How many times?
diamond
cutter's sutra.
[music]
What?  Zero.  Elsa
answered.  Oh, yeah.  The question is, how many
times was diamond mentioned in the Diamond Cut Sutra
?  Answer: zero.
Since you are
the head of the
director?  This is Gelsa, who headed it for
more than 20 years.  What is the Sanskrit word for
damond?  On a diamond.  That
is, in Sanskrit it is
vaja diamond or aimas.  Vaja also
means strength.
Vblм vbl veg is vegetables.  So, vara
is the root of the English word for vegetable.  In the
old days they would have agreed with my
wife.  They would say that vegetables
make you stronger.  And in ancient times
they really believed in this, that
vegetables are very healthy, good for your
health, so they make you stronger.
Therefore, the English word "vet vegetables"
comes from the word "vaja".  Every time
you see a diamond or someone
talks about a diamond, you should
ask why they are talking about
diamonds.  Now you are in the
Diamond
Path classes.  What should you do now?  You
must be suspicious.  What do they
want?  What messages did the Buddhas want to
send me?  What message?  Yes, this is our
diamond path.  This is the entrance to the Diamond
Road.  When a diamond has some meaning in the
diamond
cutter's sutra.  If you are not in this class,
if
you are in class, if you are
truly a student of the diamond way, you
must say, of course, it makes
sense.
So if someone, I don't know,
maybe it's too much money.
Let's answer the question without
money.  She accuses the devil of
believing that nothing ever changes.
She says, "You believe that nothing
ever changes."  Why does she
say this?  Tell me, please, answer this
into the microphone for your teacher, not for
your financial benefit, but for your own benefit?
[music]
There are some There are some people
who have to pay the teacher
$100 to get the
answer right.  OK.  OK.  Don't forget the question.
Question.  Why does the angel
blame misunderstanding on wrong
worldview?  Why is she talking to
the devil?  Do you think nothing
changes?  Of course, he doesn't think either.
You and we, we lived for several years, not like this,
without touching the diamond path.
Why do we believe that nothing
changes?  Because we see
things changing every
moment.  She blames the devil.
She blames the devil because he
goes into one of the
extremes.  If you think that things
happen from their own side,
then the result of this
belief is
that they do not change.  Therefore he says,
that is, Shla says, if you believe that
things happen this way, not from
you, if a thing exists by itself from its
own side, it cannot
change.  She couldn't change
unless she came from your
seeds.  What seeds?  Why do things
change?  your seeds
are changing.  The seed you planted, the
tree grew from it, it ended.  That
is, the seed gives energy to this tree, and
this
tree takes this energy, grows and
dies.  If things come from your
seeds, they must die, they are not
permanent.  But if they don't come from
your seeds, why should they
change if it happens this
way?  Why should this change?  And that's
why he blames him.  You are the comrade
who thinks that nothing changes.
And he says: “I didn’t say anything, I
wouldn’t say such a thing.”  No, well you believe
it, right?  Do you understand what
Geshila is talking about?  Then he accuses
her of having no
friends.  OK.  He accuses her of having
no friends.
She he says that she is lonely.  Angel.
She explains to her that she never
comes home.  Where is home?  It is in our
human mind.  You never
come here.  Maybe once a
year when you're at the Diamond Path class
at Diamond Mountain, and other times where are
you?  OK.  And then you think about how
irritable someone is.  You see, he
blames her.  The devil blames the angels for the fact that
she has no friends, that she
never even comes home to her husband.
And what does she
say?  It's not that I don't have
friends, it's that you don't have friends.
Why?  Because those friends
you think exist, they do
n't even exist.
Every time, the next time you
quarrel with your husband or start to
quarrel, think about it, remember it.
He'll probably get even more confused
.  If things do not come from
you, they cannot
exist.  First, they can't
change.  Secondly, they could not exist at all
.  You know two husbands in the
kitchen, right?  No.  A husband who
brings you pain even when you
did nothing.  There is no such thing.  Right.  I didn't
do anything.
Where?  Where is Artem, who parodies me
when I speak?  I didn't
do anything.  I think he uses it at
home.  Don't tell him, don't tell him.  I
want to talk about one person who
parodies him very well.
The wife
says: "My husband just started yelling at me
, but I didn't do anything in this
system. If the pen comes from you,
then the husband comes from you. The husband
said something to you, it comes from
you, then you will
be upset."   OK
?  If you understand where it
comes from, then you can change
things.  If you don't understand, then it doesn't
exist.  It is the thing that
always exists.  Then he told her, "You don't have
any friends."  And she says, "She
is an
angel. I am friends with everyone. I have everyone as my
friend. Not saying that I have no
friends.
Everyone in the world and in this world is my
friend. I get along with everyone. Who is speaking? Yes, an
angel who understands
seeds. All the people in the world are mine, my friends.
I love everyone, and they love me, because
I am real, because I come
from seeds. I have a real
relationship that comes from seeds.
When I get into a
relationship, I can't.
I can have this relationship because I
respect other people's relationships. I don't
yell at my husband.
I respect, I keep my vows, I
keep my promises, and I make them
keep their promises. Very
interesting. And that's why I have a good
relationship with everyone. And that means if
you understand that things come from
seeds, then you can be closer to
everything. Because it is real, it is the
truth, it is the true world. It is the
only world.
Got it? It's not that pen comes from
seeds. Everything comes from  seeds. If you
don't understand this, then you're not living in
reality, not in the real world, in a
place that doesn't exist. Then you're
crazy. That means 8 million
trillion
people. Or they're
Buddhists. I didn't say they will. And
I didn't say they could
be. So the next thing she says,
she's an angel. She's talking about the idea of
friendship. And she's not talking about the idea that
people are naturally, well, like, natural
friends, all close to me, close to
me, right? Because they are, because they
depend on me, like the world depends on
me, on my seeds.
The world depends on me. Don't tell me I have
no friends. Every time or
every time your husband tells you
you have no friends. I have a lot of
friends, I have a ton of friends, because
my mind makes up, creates everything
now. Now I think it's the
$100 question. Everybody woke up at
once.
So he says, "You're one fire."
You don't have  friends, you come home
once a year. Howl, my mind, yes, when you
go to the diamond mountain. And basically you're on your
own all the time, you don't even have
friends. He accuses her. And then she
says: "No, no, I'm friends with
everyone." And he says:
"Why?
How?  All my friends are with me because they
come from me." Okay?
The pen and everyone else come from
me. That's why they are theirs, and they like me,
they are friends, my friends,
you know? So, it's called
dependent
origination, but there's a deeper idea. You
want to hear
it? It's interdependent origination.
And I'll make it simple for you
. The
pen depends on your
seeds. Do you want it very simple or a little
simple? Okay, a little simple. The pen
depends on your seeds, so the
pen is your
friend or you are the
pen's friend, right? Because without you, you
couldn't have this friend. Got
it?
He's also your
friend. The pen is your
friend. It's dependent
origination. That's it,
listen, I'll make it simple for you
. 100
dollars. The tree depends on the seed, and
the seed depends on the tree.
How? How is it
that the
tree grows?
Wait, how did the tree come after
the seed? I wanted to repeat what he
said now. Okay.
He will polish it and answer this now. The
family creates the tree, but the tree
also  creates a seed because you can't
name You can't
name about 100 dollars. Okay, he'll
repeat it now. Your seeds made
the pen, but the pen made the
seeds. Your seeds made the pen, but
the pen made, created the seeds, so that you
could see this pen. It's a real
interdependence that occurs naturally. On
both sides, everyone says like this, like this
. Oh, I made this pen. I made
this pen, but the pen was made by your seeds.
Created your seeds.
Because there can't be seeds until they
do something. You understand, this is the
diamond
path. Pens, the pen - these are all seeds, this is the
diamond path. And everyone else knows the
usual secret. For a DCI student, everything comes
from your pens of seeds. Everything comes from
itself. So, the diamond path.
master. Yes, master of one of the
houses. The pen comes from
me. The pen comes from my seeds.
Do you understand? New
wisely. I created the pen.
And the pen comes from my seeds.
And my seeds exist because there is a
pen. If you think about  in this, and in
dependent origination, it
exists on both sides, and it's much
deeper. And they don't usually
teach this. Even 500 dollars. An
ancient, ancient
example. And when we talk about seeds,
what's the oldest, ancient example you
can give when we talk about seeds in this
case
? A spear. An example of a spear.
She received 500 dollars.
We're talking about an example of a spear.
In the old days, they didn't have
weapons, they had
spears. And at the end of the
spear they had a stick, and at the end of the spear there
was a metal tip. They
threw, yes, even during war they
used this. So is there
an agreement during these old wars? And
they say, "Let's go to lunch, then
take a break." And they all go back
to
their fortress, start
cooking. There's no good
warrior who never puts his
spear down on the ground, because they know it
will rust or break, and so they put
their spears all in a rhino together. So that
they have these tips  touched
each other so that one spear does not stand and
does not lie on the ground, so that one spear
supports the other spear. Here is this
example. The handle depends on the seeds and
the seeds depend on the handle. This is this
natural interdependent
origination. Do you understand? That's why this is the
example with the spear.
But your husband comes from you. But you also
come from your husband,
right? By the way, when you have difficulties
with another person, that is, it is
you who is
wrong, most likely, all the time, all the time,
you have a problem if you think
that this person does not come from you.
But there is also a problem that he does not know
that you come from him. If you
connect someone,
yes, you blame yourself. It
works in two ways. This is
really true, because the tree
determines the seeds. If the other
person you have a bad
relationship with him, this is proof that
you have a bad relationship. It is a
very difficult, difficult reality. Well,
how to
realize if someone tells you that
everything  The idiots, the idiots you meet,
they come from you,
right, because they're a reflection of you, it's
hard to swallow, right? And they
define you, so it's really hard for you
to swallow, right? I mean, I wanted to
add what KS was talking about earlier, about
neutral, interdependent
origination. Every time you
say, "I want to study the Diamond
Way," you're saying, "I don't
want to study philosophy, I just want to
study the Diamond Way." I just gave you the
Diamond Way. Do you
understand? So, when she argues, what's
happening here, in this debate, the angel with
the devil, you need to get into the mood of
this argument.
That is, the angel is debating with the devil, and
he says, "You're like this, you come
home, you're always alone, you come
home once a year, I see you once a year.
You make me think for 5 minutes where
all things come from.  You are
never here.  Why should I
listen to you, Liz?  You are so lonely, I
don’t want to listen to you.” And she says: “I’m
not lonely, you are lonely.  I am friends with
everyone who lives on this planet,
because they are the tree and I am the
seed.  They made me who I
am.  This is very deep.  Comrade
pens, return to
DCI.
Seeds.  OK.  The pen creates your
seeds.  Thank you.  Thank you, pen.  And the pen
says, the pen says to you: "Thank
you. If it weren't for your seeds, I
wouldn't be here. But without you, I wouldn't be
able to write with this pen. I didn't have
these seeds to see this pen."  You
see, real dependent
origination works back and
forth in two ways.  What does this
mean?  She is never alone.  Angel, and
she knows it.  If you
understand
dependence, you are in deep relationships with
every person on this planet and with
other planets, but I am not talking about
that now.  Fine?  I'll repeat it again.
If you really understand
the pen,
then you are a friend, then you connect, if
you understand the pen, every person on
this planet is your friend.  You are dependent on each
other.  Don't tell me I'm
lonely because I only show up here
once.  But I am friends with everyone, and you are not.
You are not mine, you are not my friend.  Do you understand what
he means?  He is lonely.  Who is he?  Ignorance.
Devil.  The understanding of this
world is wrong, the worldview is wrong.
Then she says very, very, she
says something very sexy.  And now she's
bragging.  You are a loser,
you are lonely, you are always alone in your
head.  I have friends, I have so many
friends, you don't even know how many.  And I
ask him: "Well, who, who, who are
your friends?"  And she
begins: "Now here is a list of all my
friends."
Sunrise.  Moonrise
sun and moon my friends.  Cool,
huh?  The direction of all my friends, East and
West, they depend on me.  Do you know what
I mean?  She brags about it.
Yes, he
accuses her of having no friends and that
she is a loser and that she has no one.  I'm a
loser and I have friends in the
highest places for you.  Where is the sun and the
moon?  So, I have east and
west.  I have day and
night.  They are my friends.
And summer, winter, autumn and spring.  Four
seasons.  They are my
friends.  The fact that
the rain falls and
that the lights ripen, that the fruits ripen,
they all come from me.  She keeps
bragging about how many friends she has.  I have
everyone as my friend.  Stanley, $100.
Now the question.
You can buy another
statue.
So he won't answer.  It's OK
.
This is what she's talking about boundaries.  She
says, she says, there is a division
between night and day.  She talks about the
division between West and East.  She speaks
between the division of summer and winter.
He has already answered in Sanskrit.  Sam.
Sam.  Sam is, you know, a
worldview,
right?  It's 50
dollars.  What does sima mean in Tibetan?
Sun.  Tell me yourself
.  So there are two words you
must learn.  In
Tibetan,
sam is ts am, in English, sam.  In
Sanskrit.
And in Tibetan it is a long pronunciation.
Sima.  Sima means the boundary of
division.
And in English
it is
sim.  Here, you see, are the seams on his
shirt that he shows.  This is the
line on the sleeve where they joined
one piece to another piece.  It
comes from the ancient Sanskrit language Sima.   The
word sutri also comes from this.
This is this line that is
overdue.  What does Sima mean?
Tima denotes the boundaries of
division.  This is
very, very important for a retreat, for a
retreat center.  This is very important for a
retreat center.  Every time we
do a
retreat, a serious retreat, we draw
these boundaries.  We make two borders.
Shala, how much, tell me, how much money will you
give for this question?
Two boundaries, at least we make, we
designate two boundaries in our
retreat.  Oh, for
what?  If someone runs up
this mountain and sticks a
stick in it, it's
called.  Either here or do you hang mantras
on the four sides of your house?  Yes.
Sima, what we call sima.  Say
sima, long pronunciation and it means
boundaries,
divisions.  And I
say, when I punched three godart
predrite, Eli, you remember, I was in the
car, I was
finishing
the book of the Sutralamazny cutter, the last
page, the translation.
And we approach the gates of this
retreat of ours.  And I gave him, her, Eli, my
translation, transcript, share of this book.  And
I got out of the car and turned my back to
the gate.  Yes, he said.  I turned to
the gate, closed the gate and said that I will
not leave this retreat for 3 years.  It's a
very strange feeling, yes, when you
hold that door, you say: "I will not leave the
3retor for 3 years, I will not
finish. I will not leave this, this
gate, this boundary of my retreat.
Strange things happened. I broke my
tooth. Really, really bad.
And at another
retreat, I need to go to the city. I
need a dentist, excuse me,
to fix my tooth. And I'm like: "What?
Let's just glue it, let's glue it, let's seal the
tooth with glue." And he said: "I don't know, but I
lost my tooth.  Where is
he?  We'll just find something and glue it with
super glue.  Let's try."
And I didn't cross those boundaries. I didn't cross
those boundaries for 3 years. I didn't leave
the retreat for 3 years. And here's the
idea. In the debate between the angel and the devil. The idea of
the Sima. What is the Sima about here?
What kind of division is there
between the pen and the seeds? Between
the sun and the moon, between the east and
the west. What project did we have in
Mexico before? Across the
border in
Dagloss, right? That is, Diamond Mountain is
already close to Mexico. If you
go up the mountain, you will see
Mexico there. Therefore, when he says across
the border, it means that there
was a project with
Mexico very close. And I say: "I need to
go there, I need to do something." I
crossed the border, started talking to
the workers and said: "Wait, I
told the police."
Can I do something? And the police
wrote off that they don't trust you.
Just for fun. I want to put
one foot in Mexico, one foot  in the States.
I want to feel what it
feels like. And I stood here with both feet
and looked at this division, this
border between Mexico and
the States. And, you know, well, it feels
exactly the same. I don't feel anything. I don't
feel any border, any divisions. I
don't see any. Just some kind of
desert, just some dirt. I don't
see anything. But this is a karmic line. In this, this,
this country, a lot of people
are hungry. And 6 feet 2 meters to the left, they have
too much food. They are all dying from
eating too much. I
mean, here these people are hungry, and here
they are dying from overeating. Sorry,
too much eating, too many
politicians
there. Your seeds create this
border. And what does she say, angel?
Borders, and my
friends, borders between you and
others, borders between your eyes and your
pen.
The division between you and me or
the border. It all comes from the seeds. It
all comes from. Sima comes from
your seeds. Do you understand? She doesn't just
say:
"You know, the sun and the east are the sun, but it
happens day and night, the west and east
happen because of me." She doesn't say
that. She he says: "You, you created these
boundaries."
By the way, if anyone, if anyone
understood this, if everyone
understood, then we would have a very
strange
language. Mi and David
went so
that David could translate into
Chinese English.
Then you need to change
all languages, because all languages
are based on misunderstanding.
You and I are a
mistake. It is not that and not that if
you are a good person, you should think of
me as yourself. That is not what it is. That is not
true. That is wrong. There should
be no you and
me. We must eat. We must
have lunch. It
doesn't matter where the boundary is. Do you understand what
I mean? I am you, and you are me. Therefore, if you
understand
it like this and your partner says to you,
the devil in your head says: "You
don't have any friends, you don't
understand that I am the only one who has
friends everywhere."  The angel says: "You are a loser,
you are lonely, you who have no friends, you do not
understand.  You cannot exist without
other people.   Do
you understand?  This is very, very strong.  And that's
why it took us 10 years to
get to this point.  This
one verse is very, very
powerful.  And when you think about it,
wisdom says: “Understanding is the seed,
understanding is the pen. I have real
friends, and you don’t even know what
friends are. I have such good friends
that we are all of them – they are me. Don’t say that
I don’t have
friends. This is the truth. I don’t have friends. I am
my
friends. And this is as
close as we are. And if you understand this, then
your life is just
cool every
day. A real holiday.
Understanding that you are these
people, this is a holiday all day long
that doesn’t
stop. You can be
kidding, laughing,
you know? And it’s cool, even fun that
all these are the things we’re
talking about, philosophy. If you want to
enjoy every day, think about
it. And it’s really joyful,
cool. It’s not just your
birthday, which comes once a
year. What deep wisdom is here?
Geshela, how old is a
student? I say 365. Everyone has a different
mood. My wife says: “Don’t
eat dessert.” And I tell her  I say: "Well,
one of my students has a
birthday today.  365 days a year, every
student has a birthday." So this
boundary of separation also comes from within
you. Maybe they are so obvious,
visible and not so useful, but they
relate to retreat. Because the word
retreat in the ancient language si in
Sanskrit sam na s Tibetan means
boundaries,
means to stay within the boundary.
Sometimes you can often think clearly
when you don’t have people around you, if
you have a family, if you work, if
you have a normal wife, it’s
good,
yes, to be with other people, but
sometimes to be alone in your cubicle, and
in mine in my
retreat. It’s very wonderful. You
know, John Brady, I have this
thing.
I remember looking out the
window during retreat and said, and this is not
fun. I remember the moment when I
looked out the window and said during my
retreat: “This is not fun.  I didn't have a
toilet, I didn't have water, I didn't
have electricity, I was just in the
desert." And I said, "This is not
fun." Why? Because there is no
one to help me.
And I
can't enjoy, be
happy, help anyone. I
felt very
lonely. Retreat is great, but
I don't have a chance
to cook dinner for someone,
to say hello to someone, to spend time with someone.
I don't have time to serve people.
Yes, I think, I think one of the reasons to
go on retreat is that, for example,
this time there will be a 4-
day
retreat, a silent retreat. I think
you will feel that you are missing
people, and you will miss people on the
third day, on the third day, you will miss
those people who even
irritated you during this silent
retreat. This is the time when you need to
think about how to be a bathisattva. To be a
bathisattva. When you are in deep retreat by
yourself for a long time  time, you
will understand how much you need other people
and how cool and sweet it is to serve other
people. Do you understand? It doesn't matter where they are, whether they are
good or not so good people.
Sometimes it's even fun to serve not so
good people.
This is just a real art. This is an
advanced art, a form of art
to serve bad people. Like, how much
time do I have left, Tim?
Then
she, she
says, she's an angel finally leaving for
another place. And she
says 333, 337 version, if someone has the
verse
open, she says, there are boundaries
between summer, winter, autumn, and then she
says, there is a boundary between being alive and
being dead. And he says
that
so there is also another boundary. She
says, it's called life and
death. There are other divisions. You may
be sick or in agony.
You can
suffer in a diamond mountain all at the
same time, in the same week, for example, from
great
heat. Compared to, if you compare a
toilet with heat, I choose heat.
You have cold
and
drought, then
There is, that is, in an unusual way, she crosses
boundaries. She talks about how we
age and how we
talk about the suffering of dying. She
says: "I also
created dividing lines between the four
truths.  I created
between pain and the cause of pain,
nerves and the path.  I created these four I
created four lines between the four
true arias, between life and
death.  If you understand these lines, these
divisions, they come from within you, you
can change it.  If you don't
understand them, you can't change them.
Fine.  If you understand the Sim, where
the Sim is, this border, yes, the divisions,
where it comes from, you can even
divide this Sim between life and
death.   Do
you understand?  This is a tantric lesson.  I can
say whatever I want.
Seiji and I are working on a special
project about
helping
people.  What will you do in the second
half of your life?  We are developing one
idea.  I taught, I gave
instruction.  And someone said to me,
"Oh, so you teach the second part of
life?"  No, I'm teaching, I'm teaching the
first part, what's going on.  Then they're
like,
"What I'm not interested in is how
you get sick, fall ill,
die, how you get old.
That's not very interesting to me. I'm
teaching you the next two lives, how you
transition, how you move from
this life to another life, how you
do it very artificially,
artificially, beautifully. That is, this is what
I teach, how it's the
first, second, second
half. What happens after that,
when you
die? If you start a new
project, when you're 40, yes, that's the
first part of your new life, and then
you become a master, you become
this art of how to do the second part of
your life. That is, don't think of life
as the first half and the second half.
Don't think of it that way. The second half of
your life is the first part of your
life. You see? And then what
happens? You die. Then you
have the second part, the second half. And
if you study well, if you
learn how to do retreats correctly,
study the Diamond Way, it's
incredibly fun, cool, it's
wonderful, it's  Super cool. Do you
know what color the sky will be in my
next
life?
Peach. Peach will be the sky of my
next life. Bet, you can
plant
the next your childhood or when you are a
teenager, a
teenager, imagine, you can plant
those seeds now. That's what I'm
talking about. And you can say, "Either I am
crazy," or he knows something. It doesn't matter
to me what you say. Even
if you say I am crazy, it doesn't
matter to me.
E, if you want to give 100 dollars,
still, maybe I am crazy
because I know something. It's possible that we
should say. Either he knows something,
or
he, maybe he knows, or maybe
he doesn't know.
Right? So, I'm waiting for
it. Let's go to the next world. Don't
be late. M.